>> Brian Holt: 新文件，保存它，在 src 中调用它，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: New file,
save it, call it inside of src,
并叫它 store.js。
and call it store.js.
在商店内，我希望您导入 createStore，
Inside of store,
I want you to import createStore,
编写并应用中间件。
compose, and apply middleware.
>> Brian Holt: 其实我们不需要应用中间件，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Actually we
don't need apply middleware,
你可以把那个出去就可以了
you can leave that one out,
so just compose.
>> Brian Holt: 我不认为你需要作曲。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: I don't think
you even need compose.
所以，请从 redux中创建 createStore 。
So just createStore from redux.
然后进口我们从 ./reduers 进口一个还原剂
Then import, we're gonna import
a reducer from ./reducers, but
我们还没做过这只是暂时的错误
we haven't made that yet, so
that will just be an error for right now.
const store = createStore(还原剂) 和
const store = createStore(reducer) and
导出缺省存储。
export default store.
>> Brian Holt: 因此，在最基本的情况下，这是 redux 的内容。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So at its most basic,
this is what redux is.
你有一个根减速器如果你还记得这个
You have one root reducer which if you
remember from the hooks section of this,
他们会看起来一模一样的对吧
they're gonna look exactly the same,
right?
这是根减速器。
So this is the root reducer.
所以它是一种老状态下的功能
So it's a function that
takes in an old state,
让你重新回到新状态
and gives you back new state.
这就是这个，它只是一个功能。
So that's what this is,
it's just a function.
这就是商店的中央存储库
And then this is the central
repository of store,
我们最终将在这里再次联系到 React
which we're going to eventually connect
to React here in just a second.
现在我们再做一件事
Now, we're gonna do one more thing here.
我们会给它这种黑魔法巫毒让我们可以利用
We're gonna give it this kind of black
magic voodoo that allows us to use
也可以使用 redux dev 工具。
the redux dev tools as well.
所以我们会说如果是 typeof window ，那么
So we're gonna say if typeof window, so
如果我们在浏览器中，那么如果这等于对象，
if we're in the browser, so
if this is equal to object and,
>> Brian Holt: 和 typeof
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And typeof
窗口。__REDUX_DEVTOOLS_EXTENSION__
window.__REDUX_DEVTOOLS_EXTENSION__
不等于未定义。
is not equal to undefined.
所以说如果我在浏览器里
So basically it's saying
if I'm in the browser and
redux dev 工具存在，让我们继续使用该工具。
the redux dev tools exist,
let's go ahead and use that.
所以如果那是真的你会说的
So if that's true, then you're gonna say.
我只复制并粘贴
I'll just copy and paste that.
调用该函数，否则，
Call that function, otherwise,
只要给它一些随机函数就可以用 F 到 F
just give it some random function to use,
so F to F.
>> Brian Holt: 因此，如果 Redux DevTools 存在，那么该代码的 blob 会再次出现，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So what this blob of code
does, again, if the Redux DevTools exists,
用它们
use them.
如果没有，就给它一些假的函数，就是这个。
If it doesn't, give it some bogus
function which is exactly what this is.
>> Brian Holt: 有道理吗 ?
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Makes sense?
好的好的我知道
Yeah, cool, from here, I know.
另一个是，如果你想用像你这样的东西，或者萨格斯，或者
The one other thing is, if you wanted to
use something like thunks, or sagas, or
可以观察到，或者类似的东西，你也会在这里做。
redux observable, or something like that,
you would do that here, as well.
我们不去了但这就是你要做的
We're not going, but
this is where you would do it.